<group name="alerts">
 <!-- Save Changes message -->
 <group name="save">
  <string id="title">
   El proyecto '{0}' tiene cambios sin guardar.
  </string>
  <string id="subtitle">
   ¿Qué es lo que quieres hacer?
  </string>
  <string id="option1">
   Guardar cambios\nGuardar el proyecto en el disco, entonces cerrar.
  </string>
  <string id="option2">
   No guardar\nDescargar los cambios.
  </string>
  <string id="option3">
   Cancela\nVolver a Construct 2.
  </string>
  <!-- Ordinary messagebox prompt for Windows XP -->
  <string id="xp">
   ¿Guardar los cambios en el proyecto '{0}'?
  </string>
 </group>
 <!-- save -->
 <!-- Shown on startup for invalid license files.  Note \n indicates a line break, since
			 line breaks and whitespace in XML tags are ignored. -->
 <string id="licenseload-fail">
  Se encontró un archivo de licencia para Construct 2, pero se produjo un error al cargarlo. Construct 2 ha vuelto a la edición gratuita.\n\nEsto puede ocurrir si el archivo está dañado, dañado o modificado de alguna manera. Si tiene una copia de seguridad del archivo de licencia, intente restaurarlo. De lo contrario, póngase en contacto con licensehelp@scirra.com e intentaremos solucionarlo tan rápido como podamos.
 </string>
 <!-- Shown on startup if the user has balloon tips disabled, which means they may not see
			 syntax error prompts in the event sheet and other notifications. -->
 <string id="balloontips-disabled">
  Los tips están parecen estar deshabilitados. No verá notificaciones de errores.
 </string>
 <!-- Shown if no exporters could be found or loaded -->
 <string id="noexporters-error">
  Failed to find or load any exporters.  The IDE cannot start up.
 </string>
 <!-- Startup alert about update checks -->
 <group name="update">
  <string id="title">
   Would you like Construct 2 to automatically check for updates online?
  </string>
  <string id="subtitle">
   No personal information is sent to Scirra.  You may see a warning about Construct 2 attempting to access the Internet.
  </string>
  <!-- \n separates option title and subtitle -->
  <string id="option1">
   Check for updates (recommended)
  </string>
  <string id="option2">
   Check for beta updates\nHelp test new versions of Construct 2.  Beta releases introduce new features sooner, but are more likely to have problems.
  </string>
  <string id="option3">
   Don't check for updates
  </string>
  <!-- Shown if user chooses 'Don't check for updates' -->
  <string id="noupdates">
   Construct 2 will not check for updates.  Be sure to check the Scirra.com website regularly for updates which may include new features and bug fixes.  You can change your update setting in the Preferences dialog.
  </string>
 </group>
 <!-- update -->
 <!-- Startup alert about out-of-date graphics card drivers -->
 <group name="gfxdriver">
  <string id="title">
   The driver for your graphics card ({0}) appears to be over 2 years old.
  </string>
  <string id="subtitle">
   Old drivers can cause crashes and glitches in Construct 2.  It is strongly recommended that you check for an updated version of your driver to make sure it does not cause problems in Construct 2.
  </string>
  <!-- For the Vista+ task dialog options.  \n separates the option title and subtitle -->
  <string id="option1">
   Take me to a web site which can help me update my driver\nThis is strongly recommended to ensure the best possible experience while using Construct 2.
  </string>
  <string id="option2">
   Ignore this message\nGo back to Construct 2 without checking for a driver update (not recommended).  You may experience crashes or glitches caused by your graphics card driver.
  </string>
  <!-- Option given on Windows XP, which does not support task dialogs -->
  <string id="xpoption">
   Would you like to be taken to a web site which can help you update your driver?
  </string>
 </group>
 <!-- gfxdriver -->
</group>
